

Roland Jethro Suyom

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Having three years of experience in coding, developing, and maintaining websites and applications. Adept at coordinating effectively with development teams and clients to execute brilliant projects. Excited to pursue new companies to grow my skills while ameliorate to their goals and success.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer, Freelance / Project-based

2020 - PRESENT

- Enhanced 10+ responsive websites for clients in a variety of industries.
- Implemented a ticketing app for a start-up company that added 20% more to its profit.
- Collaborated with developers, QA testers, and cross-functional teams ensuring projects will have 100% product functionality.
- Produced a RESTful API that allowed for seamless integration with other applications.
- Improved a business application performance by 20% by optimizing the front-end code.

Internships / Trainings

Mobile Developer, Agro-Digital PH

SEPTEMBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

• Designed and contributed to developing a mini marketplace mobile app for farmers that helped them gain 20% more of their income.

Backend Developer, Zuri Internship

MARCH 2021 - JULY 2021

 Managed a back-end development team to provide APIs needed for a KidVacc project. It was intended to allow parents/guardians in Africa to receive their children's vaccinations.

Front-End Developer, HNG Internship

JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Created a beautiful and responsive website for the Envato project.
- Developed a secure, interactive web application with a modern front-end framework and an intuitive user interface.

Projects

https://github.com/Jeth0214

https://jethcode.com/

Education

JE Mondejar Foundation College Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Tacloban City, Philippines College Level

Contact

Bulacan

Philippines

+966530095815

+639451736037

rolandjethrosuyom@yahoo.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitiHub

Peronal Websites

Tech Stack

HTML

CSS /SASS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

Angular

PHP

MySQL/SQL

Laravel

Ionic

Git

NPM

Language

Filipino

Arabic

English